[Music]
[音乐]
这张卡是情人卡，我
this card is a Valentine's card and I
称呼这里是这里
基于M折教程19
this card is a Valentine's card and I
call it shower of hearts here it is this
EM折叠的方式基本上是
建立了急性V形折叠的急性V形折叠
call it shower of hearts here it is this
is based on an M fold tutorial 19 this
进入沟渠，但全部做成一个
这是教程19，然后实际
is based on an M fold tutorial 19 this
is how the em fold goes it's basically
事实上，它的柜台褶皱增加了
添加到所有折痕中
is how the em fold goes it's basically
an acute V fold with acute v-folds built
那是教程22，所以这是M折
加上猫和折痕给您
an acute V fold with acute v-folds built
into the gullies but all made in one so
这些反折可以给您更多
可以像
into the gullies but all made in one so
this is tutorial 19 and then in actual
这你会看到所有的小
不同的飞机得到了这些武器
this is tutorial 19 and then in actual
fact that as counter folds added to it
用心和东西粘在他们身上
最后，我将向您展示如何
fact that as counter folds added to it
added into all the creases
很快就成为其中之一
对折的基片
added into all the creases
that's tutorial 22 so here's an M fold
完全弄皱了，这将是
M折，所以我们再次将其折入
that's tutorial 22 so here's an M fold
with added cats and creases giving you
半
我们从大约
with added cats and creases giving you
these counter folds that give you more
这样的事情的三分之一
像这样折回两侧
these counter folds that give you more
planes that can all be extended like
所以我们有两个角度，你打开
它在那下面的每一侧向上倾斜
planes that can all be extended like
this you'll see that all the little
点他们都是一样的，然后你
只需将它的一侧折叠起来
this you'll see that all the little
different planes have got these arms
折痕一定要远离
脊椎一定不能到同一点
different planes have got these arms
stuck onto them with hearts and stuff on
其他所有
是我所以你只是把它折叠起来
stuck onto them with hearts and stuff on
the end so I'll just show you how to
像这样的东西折叠回来
本身，然后在另一边
the end so I'll just show you how to
make one of those really quickly here's
不必与我们可以一样
折起来，我们再次创造它倾斜
make one of those really quickly here's
a base sheet folded in half
远离中间折线
回到自己，现在我们可以
a base sheet folded in half
creased really thoroughly this will be
六角琴，所以这些褶皱来了
向前棘手，我们在那里，然后
creased really thoroughly this will be
the M fold so again we just fold it in
像这样折起来
折起所有这些将成为您的M折
the M fold so again we just fold it in
half
我会稍微修剪一下
太大
half
we cut a wedge out of the up to about
就这样回来了
现在我们的柜台都折叠了
we cut a wedge out of the up to about
third of the way up something like that
这些折痕，我什至可以做到
稍低一点，因为我们要
third of the way up something like that
fold the two sides back like this
必须做握住心灵的手臂
会突出很多
fold the two sides back like this
so we've got the two angles and you open
在任何这些折痕上都像这样
你可以再剪一些折
so we've got the two angles and you open
it up the angles on each side below that
在自己身上，然后再次推动
通过，所以我们又产生了两个
it up the angles on each side below that
point they're both the same and then you
那里可以添加东西的飞机
给他们这个也许我们不会削减
point they're both the same and then you
just take one side fold it up now this
如果你看的话，我们会把它折叠起来
教程22您将看到所有
just take one side fold it up now this
crease must be leaning out away from the
您可以添加计数器的不同方式
折叠到弹出窗口上的折痕
crease must be leaning out away from the
spine it mustn't come to the same point
我们去
所以你有一些其他的东西
spine it mustn't come to the same point
where all the other
以及
因此产生了更多的飞机
where all the other
is me so you just have it folding up
可以扩展，所以现在我将
坚持下去这是一个页面
is me so you just have it folding up
something like this fold that back on
基本的锐角v折就是
这一切的核心，随着页面的关闭
something like this fold that back on
itself and then on the other side it
这将向前折叠，所以你想要
该页面位于页面顶部附近
itself and then on the other side it
doesn't have to be the same we can just
和所有这些事情一样
确保角度匹配我们刚放的
doesn't have to be the same we can just
fold it up and again we creat it leaning
一侧的胶水先粘下来
中央折痕与
fold it up and again we creat it leaning
out away from the middle fold so fold
基本卡上的中央折痕可以
看看你认为会看到你的角度
out away from the middle fold so fold
that back on itself and now we can
坐好，这对我来说看起来不错
然后把它折下来，关上胶水
that back on itself and now we can
concertina this so these folds come
其他选项卡始终将其涂抹
折痕粘到折痕是
concertina this so these folds come
forward tricky there we are and then
实际的重要方面
外边缘并不重要
forward tricky there we are and then
fold that back when it comes like this
然后我们关闭发现的基地
它的自然黏附位置
fold that back when it comes like this
crease it all this will be your M fold
您现在可以开始
只是这些小碎片和小武器，
crease it all this will be your M fold
I'll just trim it down a bit it's a bit
你可以把它们伸出来
真的有任何角度，所以你只要把它们
I'll just trim it down a bit it's a bit
too big
这样说
这样，您需要每次检查
too big
that's it back something like this and
经常，当您将它们添加到
确保他们不会
that's it back something like this and
now we have the counter folds into all
该地方关闭时发生冲突，所以我们关闭了
这和你是的，到目前为止很好
now we have the counter folds into all
these creases I might even make that
这样我们就出来了
在我实际割下的手臂上加一下手臂
these creases I might even make that
slightly lower because we're going to
所有这些笔直的他们可能会弯曲
但是你可以出来这样说
slightly lower because we're going to
have to do the arms that hold the hearts
您开始创建一个相当
复杂有趣的几乎
have to do the arms that hold the hearts
will be jutting out quite a lot sort of
的网络，但这只是一系列的武器
伸出来，然后可以添加
will be jutting out quite a lot sort of
stake like that on any of these creases
我会再次检查的心
确保一切都好，而且不断
stake like that on any of these creases
you can have extra cuts fold them back
认为你没有我就知道了
必然需要建立更多的
you can have extra cuts fold them back
on themselves and back again push that
这些我在这里有一些很大的心
但还不够，我只是把奇怪
on themselves and back again push that
through so we've generated two more
一个就可以了
印象，所以把胶水放在手臂上
through so we've generated two more
planes there that can have things added
而不是在你心中
粘上你总是把胶水
planes there that can have things added
to them this one maybe we won't cut it
最小的表面而不是更大的表面
工作，所以我认为这可能是
to them this one maybe we won't cut it
we'll just fold it if you look at
足够让您了解如何
作品
we'll just fold it if you look at
tutorial 22 you'll just see all the
然后您就可以逐步构建它，
随心所欲地保持复杂
tutorial 22 you'll just see all the
different ways that you can add counter
检查，它将像这样工作
而且他们不会与之发生冲突
different ways that you can add counter
folds to the creases on the pop-up
彼此表示武器不会
纠结起来，然后你实际上可以
there we go
在其他各种类型上使用此技术
基本的机制，所以这里有一个
so you have things some on this other
这是基于一种扭曲
机制，这是教程17
so you have things some on this other
side as well
卡还不够弯曲
应该就这样消失了，但是
so generated quite a few more planes
我真的很感兴趣，这就是全部
不同的手臂，上面贴着一朵花
so generated quite a few more planes
that can be extended so now I'll just
结束，所以这是一个例子
的
that can be extended so now I'll just
stick this down to the page this is a
当你打开它的机制
六架飞机，这里有两架
stick this down to the page this is a
basic acute angle v-fold that's the
然后在下面有两个
在这里，所以任何人都可以拥有武器
basic acute angle v-fold that's the
heart of it all and as the page closes
伸出鲜花或心形
卡在最后你也可以
heart of it all and as the page closes
that's going to fold forward so you want
如果你有一个反极
额外的切割，你可以弯曲下来
that's going to fold forward so you want
this to be up near the top of your page
向后弯曲，将其推过，如此
再一次，你就是你创造的
this to be up near the top of your page
and as with all these things to make
另外两架飞机，所以你可以做到
遍及整个过程
and as with all these things to make
sure that the angles match we just put
类似其他机制
可以使用锯齿形折叠
sure that the angles match we just put
the glue on one side first stick it down
这是教程20的曲折
我已经削减了一些
the glue on one side first stick it down
with this central crease flush with the
本来是这样的
然后我增加了额外的削减
with this central crease flush with the
central crease on the base card you can
所以它产生更多的飞机，你
可以拿起这些小武器，你可以
central crease on the base card you can
see what angle you think would see you
让他们闭嘴闭嘴
每次都再次以奇怪的角度出现
see what angle you think would see you
sit best this looks pretty good to me
你添加东西关闭它，我有一个
夫妇在这里伸出来那些可能是
sit best this looks pretty good to me
then you fold it down shut put glue on
修剪掉了，但您只是继续添加
武装它建立一个复杂的
then you fold it down shut put glue on
the other tab smear it always right up
一连串的武器，然后你可以坚持
你的心，花或星星或
the other tab smear it always right up
to the creases glue up to the crease is
无论您想滑行
大概有点害怕，然后
to the creases glue up to the crease is
the important aspect of this the actual
再次，您可以添加到那些，所以你做一个
每个人都有更复杂的结构
the important aspect of this the actual
outer edges don't really matter so much
这样回去
我还有一个下来
outer edges don't really matter so much
and then we shut the base which finds
离开那一个，当然他们
不必实际卡在
and then we shut the base which finds
its natural sticking position that's
结束，以便您知道可能在这里放一个
给它一件T恤，这样所有这些都可以
its natural sticking position that's
your starting point now you can take
让其他的心再次粘在他们身上
只要关闭它，确保一切正常
your starting point now you can take
just these little pieces little arms and
我已经在这里烦死了
超出边缘，但这就是事实
just these little pieces little arms and
you can stick them out just hang out at
用波普尔，你必须做假人，
做实验，看看一切
you can stick them out just hang out at
any angle really so you just put them
实际上适合您适合
当您关闭底座时，
any angle really so you just put them
say like this
您了解基本技术
我在这里用过另一种类型的
like that and you need to check it every
机制，这是基于
传播罗伯茨一本佛教著作《爱丽丝》
like that and you need to check it every
so often and as you add them just to
在仙境中，所以这是基于
提升小3D形状的艺术
so often and as you add them just to
make sure they're not going to be
他们实际上是被卡住的矩形吗
放在他们身上，但他们可以一样容易
make sure they're not going to be
clashing as the place closes so we shut
是心，我只向你展示那一个
在萨博尼斯书中，这是罗伯特的
clashing as the place closes so we shut
this and you yeah so far so good
佛陀爱丽丝梦游仙境和
尽头是拱门
there we go coming out like this you can
提出这些小的3D形状，然后
扑克牌全都卡住了
there we go coming out like this you can
add arms on to arms I've actually cut
他们创造了一个非常惊人的混乱
效果这是我在这里所做的是
add arms on to arms I've actually cut
all these straight they could be curved
类似的东西正在创造一个
这可能是心中的混乱效应
all these straight they could be curved
but you could come out say like this so
关闭时显然很粗糙
你可以看到他们都伸出来了
but you could come out say like this so
you're starting to create quite a
我需要再做一个边缘
考虑到一切
you're starting to create quite a
complicated interesting sort of almost
缩小尺寸，使其停留在底部，因此
实际上没有关于如何
complicated interesting sort of almost
of web but it's just an array of arms
做一个拱门，所以我只告诉你
快速地制作拱形，这样你
of web but it's just an array of arms
sticking out that you can then add the
可以建立
这是您的基本表
sticking out that you can then add the
hearts to I'll just check again make
要建立一个基本上是急性的
建立在其上的角度v形折叠
hearts to I'll just check again make
sure that it's all okay and on and on I
所以我们把一半折成两半
这就是教程中的全部内容-如何制作
sure that it's all okay and on and on I
think you get the idea without me
锐角折好折
这是折痕，所以你
think you get the idea without me
necessarily needing to to build more of
将它折成一点角度
请看清楚，然后剪下
necessarily needing to to build more of
these I got some quite big hearts here
下来制作几个粘合标签
这将粘在后面
these I got some quite big hearts here
but not really enough I just put the odd
像这样的页面，但您希望它成为
拱门，所以如果你只是剪拱门的话
but not really enough I just put the odd
one on so you can get the basic
离开然后随机粘贴
可能会使其有点扭曲
one on so you can get the basic
impression so put the glue on the arms
形状不是很稳定，所以您
首先需要你算出什么
impression so put the glue on the arms
rather than on the hearts when you're
您想要基本弹出窗口的角度
但是你为什么还要走更多
rather than on the hearts when you're
gluing you always put the glue on the
它会躺下来，你变得更狭窄
在底座上，它会站立得更多，所以
gluing you always put the glue on the
smallest surface rather than the larger
现在一样会这样
您需要在一侧标记角度
working so I think that's probably
它粘在哪里，所以拿一支铅笔
在这里我标记了这个角度，然后
working so I think that's probably
enough so you get the idea of how it
真正重要的是，您还标记了
边缘的末端，所以这是线
enough so you get the idea of how it
works
这是真正的结束
关键的事情现在你可以剪弓
works
and you can just build it up and up and
出来，所以我们将像
这个
and you can just build it up and up and
up as complicated as you like just keep
我要去之前我坚持下去
我要再折一次
up as complicated as you like just keep
checking and it's gonna work like this
只是在顶部，所以给它一个
我觉得佛陀多一点兴趣
checking and it's gonna work like this
and that they aren't gonna clash with
在他的《爱丽丝梦游仙境》示例中
不，这是我们要坚持的
and that they aren't gonna clash with
each other that the arms aren't going to
扎根于基地，因此重要
事情是你坚持减少反对
each other that the arms aren't going to
tangle up and and snag you can actually
线，你把外面的边缘
反对那个标志，所以你知道
tangle up and and snag you can actually
use this technique on all sorts of other
第一次测试时的确切位置
所以把胶水放在线的一侧
use this technique on all sorts of other
basic mechanisms so there's one here
进入最后的标记，然后您可以
把整个东西都关上，放上胶水
basic mechanisms so there's one here
this one is based on a twisting
另一个标签并关闭底座
这是你现在可以做的弓形
this one is based on a twisting
mechanism which is tutorial 17 this bit
像你一样将其他部分重新构建
关闭它，你会看到这是一个假人
mechanism which is tutorial 17 this bit
hasn't quite work the cards too bendy it
那些突出的片段无关紧要
我们不妨修剪一下
hasn't quite work the cards too bendy it
should have gone gone like that but what
只是他们都适合基地
请现在关闭它，没关系
should have gone gone like that but what
I'm really interested in here is all the
现在我们将添加一些小块
因此，最简单的方法就是
I'm really interested in here is all the
different arms with a flower stuck onto
采取绝对最简单的方法
这只是将标签折叠到一端
different arms with a flower stuck onto
the end of it so this is an example of
在上面放胶
折叠成一个循环，这样你就可以循环
the end of it so this is an example of
the
这样，然后压扁
再将它对半折叠
the
mechanism when you open that up it's got
现在，当您打开它时，它会重新回到自身
你有一个正方形，所以你
mechanism when you open that up it's got
six planes it's got two on the top here
可以把它粘到那个沟渠里
拱加入页面，在此之前
six planes it's got two on the top here
then it's got two underneath here and
再次，我将添加几个小柜台
褶皱我会在那儿做个切口
then it's got two underneath here and
here and so any of those can have arms
向后弯，现在就推
这不只是产生一个
here and so any of those can have arms
sticking out with flowers or hearts
我们已经产生了另外两架飞机
您可以粘贴的额外四架飞机
sticking out with flowers or hearts
stuck on the end you can also make
多余的胶水整体上
很多
stuck on the end you can also make
counter poles of these if you have a
确保此折痕紧贴
那沟壑就在那里，然后我们将
counter poles of these if you have a
extra cut there you can bend this down
关闭底座并按好它，使
如果我们再做一次的话，那一定能奏效
extra cut there you can bend this down
bend it back push that through and so
我会在另一边做类似的事情
向您展示制作它的另一种方式
bend it back push that through and so
again there you are you've created
这次只是想出一个角度
在这种情况下，我们不需要这么大的一块
again there you are you've created
another two planes so you can do that
我不会使其完整循环
我会做这样的事
another two planes so you can do that
all over it and end up creating
折成一半的折痕
所以可能就像那对标签
all over it and end up creating
something like this other mechanisms
这将像这样粘在上面
所以它向中间倾斜
something like this other mechanisms
that you can use of the zigzag fold so
或者你实际上可以拥有另一个
这样它实际上就从
that you can use of the zigzag fold so
this is tutorial 20 is a zigzag fold
我认为在这种情况下我很中间
像它向中间倾斜一样
this is tutorial 20 is a zigzag fold
I've made a couple of cuts as it stood
这不是这样的循环，所以你已经
有折痕放入沟渠中
I've made a couple of cuts as it stood
originally it would have been like this
必须测量它，所以您只需将其放入
这样，中央的折痕
originally it would have been like this
and then I've added extra cuts increases
基地紧紧地扎在那沟里
只是标记出其中一个折痕所在
and then I've added extra cuts increases
so it's generating more planes and you
在底座上只是标记它的末端，这样
您要确保确切知道
so it's generating more planes and you
can take these little arms and you can
一块去，现在你翻转它
结束，所以我把折痕放到那个沟里
can take these little arms and you can
stick them on shutting up shutting out
现在你要把它翻转过来
像这样坚持下去，我会
coming up at odd angles again every time
放一些胶水，你只在一侧粘
这次我把它放在那个标记上
coming up at odd angles again every time
you add stuff shut it down I've got a
紧紧向下移动，将其粘在
其他标签将胶水涂抹到边缘，然后
you add stuff shut it down I've got a
couple sticking out here those could be
然后关闭找到它的基地
在地球上的自然黏附的地方
couple sticking out here those could be
trimmed off but you just keep adding
因此，现在这两个
这在这里创造了一个沟壑
trimmed off but you just keep adding
arms to it building up a complicated
在这里您可以建造更多这些
这些较小或相同的尺寸
arms to it building up a complicated
array of arms that you can then stick
同样在这里您可以在其中建立更多
如果我们看一下这个
array of arms that you can then stick
your hearts or flowers or stars or
它结束了，你可以看到那里有一个正方形
一个，有一个倾斜的柜台文件夹
your hearts or flowers or stars or
whatever you feel like onto gliding
与此相同，实际上
内置了三层
whatever you feel like onto gliding
around a bit I'm afraid no and then
一二三然后你就开始
粘贴并粘贴
around a bit I'm afraid no and then
again you can add to those so you make a
自己，然后建立这个
一点一点哦，我还有另一种方式
again you can add to those so you make a
more complicated structure with everyone
告诉你坚持到这里
像这样折成一半你可以
more complicated structure with everyone
going back like this
你可以做一个捷径
把它自己折叠起来，所以我切入
I have another one coming coming down
从折痕边缘将其折叠
这样回来，所以这块看起来像
I have another one coming coming down
off that one there and of course they
再次将其折叠起来
然后当您弹出它，所以我们弹出
off that one there and of course they
don't have to actually be stuck on the
通过这个给你
这样的形状，现在这是这个
don't have to actually be stuck on the
end so you can know maybe put one here
这是绝对标准的柜台
折叠，你可以把胶水一直
end so you can know maybe put one here
give it a t-shirt so all of these can
左右两边都很好涂
然后把这个折痕收紧
give it a t-shirt so all of these can
have other hearts stuck onto them again
甘尼
这样又给你两架飞机
have other hearts stuck onto them again
just close it make sure it's all working
玩关闭它，确保它
所有的作品，所以你就可以开始
just close it make sure it's all working
I've goofed here it's actually sticking
建立你的心像
这个，你可以坚持下去
I've goofed here it's actually sticking
out of the edge but that's the thing
坚持，那是心中的沐浴
情人卡
out of the edge but that's the thing
with popper you have to make dummies and
[音乐]
[掌声]
with popper you have to make dummies and
experiment and just see that everything
[音乐]